<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<document xmlns="http://maven.apache.org/XDOC/2.0" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
	xsi:schemaLocation="http://maven.apache.org/XDOC/2.0 http://maven.apache.org/xsd/xdoc-2.0.xsd">
	<properties>
		<title>Java Kick-Start (jaks)</title>
		<author email="jason@lilypepper.com">Jason Smith</author>
	</properties>
	<body>
		<section name="Java Kick-Start (jaks)">
			<p>It's entirely too difficult to create a standalone application with Java. I mean, 
			it's moderately painful to create an app with standard POSIX-compliant command-line options, 
			help available from the command-line, man pages, and support for i18n. This stuff ought to be 
			easy. Somebody else should take care of it so you can just concentrate on writing a great app. 
			Am I right?</p>

            <p>Jaks is still pre-alpha. When completed, it will provide a simplified path for creating 
            professional standalone Java applications. The plan is to make it easy to handle command-line 
            options, with assistance in developing help and documentation (man pages, Maven site docs). 
            I'd also like to simplify creating installation packages for Debian/Ubuntu at first, and 
            perhaps branch out later into other OSs.</p>
            
            <p>The code for this project is still under initial development, and, well, you know how the
            documentation always lags behind even that. For now, take a look in 
            <a href="./jaks-examples/index.html">jaks-examples</a> if you are curious.
            Since the documentation is incomplete, it would probably help most to look at the 
            <a href="http://code.google.com/p/java-simple-application-framework/source/browse/#svn%2Ftrunk%2Fjaks-examples%2Fsrc%2Fmain%2Fjava%2Fcom%2Fgooglecode%2Fjaks%2Fexamples">source code</a>. 
            </p>
            
            <p><a href="./jaks-quickstart/usage.html">Just show me how to get started.</a></p>
		</section>
	</body>
</document>